I have to grab his belt!
（バトムンフ）早く廻(まわ)しを！
（佑真(ゆうま)）ンッ…
Lower block!
下段払い！
（バトムンフ）ウウッ！
（佑真）逆突き！
Reverse strike!
Joint strikes!
合わせ突き！
Inside leg trip!
内掛け！
Partial Lunge
Castle
Break
Punch
Partial Lunge: Castle Break Punch!
Partial Lunge
Castle
Break
Punch
Partial Lunge
Castle
Break
Punch
目が死んでいない！　いや…
There's still life in his eyes!
No...
Trust the team.
（佑真）信じろ みんなを
Trust them and keep fighting.
信じて進め！
打て！　腕が ちぎれるまで！
Keep hitting him until your arms fall off!
Put it all on the line!
出し切れ！
みんながくれた俺の全てを！
Everything this team has given me!
アアッ…　ハァ…
East side wins!
（審判）東の勝ち！
They did it.
（金盛(かなもり)）
やりやがった ０−２の窮地から
They pulled it back from 2-0 down.
Dachi High has tied the match at 2-2!
（沙田(さだ)）
ダチ高が追いついた！　２−２！
They took it to the last bout!
（金盛）
大将戦まで もつれ込んだぞ！
（アナウンス）
突き出しで 東 五條(ごじょう)君の勝ち！
Gojo-kun wins by pushing
his opponent out of the ring.
Hey, Gojo!
（千比路(ちひろ)）ウオ〜ッ！　五條！
（佑真）おい！
Hey!
You took down a national-treasure-in-waiting!
国宝級相手に大金星だぜ！
この野郎！
That's insane!
Yuma-san!
（小関(おぜき)）佑真さん　フフッ…
Has this win taken me one step closer
to making it up to you?
これで
少しは お前に返せたのかな…
All right!
Gojo-san was amazing, wasn't he?
（千鶴子(ちづこ)）すごいですね 五條さん
I just wish we were there...
（蛍(けい)）僕らも あの場で
喜びを分かち合いたかったな
so we could celebrate with them.
I'm so happy for you, Yuma.
（礼奈）良かったね 佑真
But it's not over yet.
でも まだ終わりじゃない
Yuma and the rest of the team
have given their all
佑真や みんなが
頑張ってきたのも—
全ては あいつに つなげるため！
to present him with a chance!
Bout 12
"Onimaru Kunitsuna and Dojikiri Yasutsuna Go Again"
（咲(さき)）あっ…
Bat...
（加納(かのう)）バト…
悔しいだろうな　突き合いで
押し込んだ場面も そうだが—
He must be devastated.
You could see it when
he bested Gojo in strikes, too.
単純に相撲の実力だけで言ったら
ヤツのほうが上だったはず
He was the stronger
sumo wrestler on paper.
Paper, shmaper. Gojo won.
（沙田）それでも 勝ったのは五條
He didn't hesitate to whip out the
trump cards he'd kept up his sleeve.
この一戦のために隠していた
手の内を惜しみなく さらして—
何度も
バトの不意をつきましたからね
He caught Bat off-guard several times.
そして 終盤の怒濤(どとう)のラッシュ
And that final, furious barrage...
まるで残弾全てを
撃ち尽くすかのような—
He was putting every ounce of energy
he had into those strikes.
すさまじい連打
If you're looking for a reason Bat lost,
強いて敗因を探すとしたら—
彼にとって 通過点に
すぎなかった この一戦が—
it's because while the bout was
just a pitstop on his journey,
it meant everything to Gojo.
五條には
全てだったってところでしょう
Boss...
兄貴…
（天王寺(てんのうじ)）ひっどい顔やな みんな
Why the long faces?
We haven't lost this match yet.
まだチームの負けが
決まったわけでもないのに
I guess it's my fault for losing to Kusanagi.
俺が 草薙(くさなぎ)に
負けたりせんかったら—
If only I hadn't,
the team wouldn't be all doom and gloom.
こんな空気には
なっとらんのやろうな
（天王寺）みんなに
心配かけとるのは分かっとったが…
I knew you guys had been worried about me,
俺を もう一度—
but seeing you so fired up about giving me
another shot at Kusanagi has inspired me.
草薙に会わせようと燃えとる
みんなの背中が頼もしくてな
You all produced great sumo out there.
ええ相撲やったで みんな
みんなって…　本当に見てたのか？
俺のは ひどいもんだったろう
All of us? What bout were you watching?
I stunk up the place.
I watched your bout, yeah.
見とったさ　確かに負けはしたが
ええ顔しとったで
You may have lost,
but you looked good in the ring.
I caused you the most trouble, Aki.
お前には
いちばん世話かけたな アキ
And you stop crying too, Bat.
（天王寺）バト　お前もや　泣くな
（バトムンフ）あっ…
This is a team match.
これは団体戦や
Hold your head high till
all the bouts have been contested.
全ての戦いが終わるまで
ビシッとせい
You're a member of
the champion Hakuro team.
お前も王者白楼(はくろう)の一員やろう
負けても それは変わらんのや
Losing doesn't change that fact.
アア…　はい！
Yes, sir.
That goes for all of you!
お前らもやで　いつまで
お通夜みたいになっとんねん
Stop looking so miserable!
Let's get fired up for the fifth bout!
大将戦を盛り上げんかい！
Hakuro! Hakuro! Hakuro!
白楼！　白楼！　白楼！　白楼！
（男性）そうだ
That's right. They may have tied
the score, but Hakuro's captain...
追いつかれたとはいえ
白楼の大将は…
Even after losing to Kusanagi,
he's still acting like a yokozuna.
（駿海(しゅんかい)）草薙に敗れても なお
横綱として振る舞い続けるか
（柴木山(しばきやま)）見る者によっては
それが虚勢だと…
Some people would label that
display just now as empty bravado.
滑稽だと
思う者もいるかもしれませんね
Still, he continues to show them
what they want to see.
（駿海）
だが 皆が望む姿を見せ続ける
That is the responsibility of a yokozuna.
それも また横綱としての責務
そして 土俵に上がってしまえば
己を遮るものは何もない
And once he steps into the sumo ring,
nothing stands in his way.
内に秘めた激情が あふれ出す
The intensity he's been
holding back is unleashed.
I regret how I approached
my bout against Kusanagi.
（天王寺）草薙戦 俺は後悔しとる
なぜ気持ちまで
“挑戦者”になってもうたんか
Why did I let myself feel
like I was the underdog?
No matter what anyone says, I am
the greatest high school sumo wrestler.
誰が何と言おうと
高校相撲の頂点は俺や！
I will not lose again.
もう誰にも負けん！　俺が横綱や！
I am the yokozuna!
（火ノ丸(ひのまる)）それでいい
That's just fine.
I'm here to defeat you as a yokozuna!
（火ノ丸）ワシは
横綱のあんたに勝ちに来たんじゃ！
Thanks, you guys.
（火ノ丸）ありがとうよ みんな
みんなの頑張りがあったから
ワシは今 ここに立てている
It's thanks to all your efforts
that I'm standing here now.
いや みんなだけじゃねえ
No, not just our team's efforts...
ワシには
礼を言わなきゃならん人が—
There are so many people I need to thank.
たくさんいるんじゃ
（佑真）なら 勝たねえとな
（桐仁(きりひと)）…だな
In that case, you'd better win.
Yeah.
ぜってえ負けんじゃねえぞ！
Losing's not an option!
Go win this, Ushio!
（小関）勝ってこい 潮(うしお)！
（火ノ丸）おう！
Yeah!
横綱になろうってヤツが
２度も負けるわけにはいかねえ
Someone who wants to be a yokozuna
can't afford to lose twice.
何より
みんながくれた このチャンス—
More than anything...
They worked hard to give me this chance.
I'm not about to waste it!
絶対ムダにはしねえ！
Fifth bout. On the east side, Ushio-kun.
（アナウンス）
大将戦 東 潮君　西 天王寺君
On the west side, Tennoji-kun.
火ノ丸が敗れたのは２日前
Hinomaru lost to him two days ago.
Can anything really have changed
in such a short amount of time?
この僅かな間に
果たして 変われるのか
変わるさ
Yes, it can.
力士とは刹那を生きる者
刹那もあれば力士は変われる
Sumo wrestlers live in the moment.
And all they need to transform is a moment.
（火ノ丸）
２日前と違うのは あんたも同じ
You're a different wrestler from
the one you were two days ago, too.
Hands on the ground!
（審判）手をついて！
Which means I'll also have to
become stronger myself!
なら ワシも もっと強く！
（観客たちの どよめき）
（典馬(てんま)）低い！
He's low.
いつもより更に
Even lower than usual.
We're both in the same boat.
We've each lost a bout this tournament.
（天王寺）俺と君は同じ
一度 敗れ去った者同士や
だからこそ 侮るわけにはいかん
That is why I can't take this bout lightly.
I know your body must also feel
this power willing us to a comeback!
君の体にも満ちとるであろう—
この這(は)い上がろうとする力を…
Spirit!
（審判）はっきよい！
I won't let your forearm
charge hit me again!
（火ノ丸）
かち上げは もう食わん！
（加納）あっ…
（小関）よし！
Yes!
（火ノ丸）右下手！　させねえ！
Lock my right arm?
Not happening!
Don't stop! Keep pressing forward!
止まるな！　たたみかけろ！
Demon Wheel!
鬼車(おにぐるま)！
He was expecting it!
読まれとる！
Left arm latch-on!
（天王寺）左片閂(ひだりかたかんぬき)
（礼奈）極(き)まった！？
He's in trouble!
（咲）あっ 下手(したて)を離して…
He let go of his belt!
（火ノ丸）すくい投げ！
Belt-less arm throw!
I've researched this move, too!
（天王寺）
そのパターンも研究済みや！
Arm-lock twist down!
小手ひねり！
And I know... this move!
（火ノ丸）
そのパターンも知っとる！
は… 速い！
They're fast!
２人は
一戦を経て 互いの理解を深めた
After their first bout, they understand
more about who they're facing.
Try this on for size!
（火ノ丸）これなら どうじゃ！
天王寺に憧れ
その相撲を追い続けた火ノ丸
Hinomaru has idolized Tennoji
and evolved his sumo to match his.
I know that one, too!
それも済みや！
Through research and anticipation,
研究と想像で
どんな相手も丸裸にしてきた天王寺
Tennoji has stripped every
opponent of his weapons.
They know each others' special moves.
互いに手の内を知り尽くした者同士
They read each other
and are themselves read in turn.
次の手を読んでは読まれを
繰り返しながら—
互いの勝ち筋をつぶし合う
They continually shut down
each others' strategies.
だが この展開が続くと…
But if this keeps up...
Hinomaru's getting pushed
away more and more.
（柴木山）火ノ丸が
押し込まれる場面が増えてきた
（駿海）長きにわたり
第一線で闘い続けた経験 場数の差
When you factor in the number of battles
they've fought at the top level
and the difference in experience,
the first one to run out of pieces will be...
先に手札が尽きるのは…
Hinomaru!
火ノ丸！
Incredible.
（火ノ丸）
すげえ…　のみ込まれる！
I'm getting swallowed whole.
This is the beast Kuze Sosuke awakened...
Tennoji's true form!
これが 久世草介(くぜそうすけ)が
目覚めさせた本当の天王寺
A blackness that occludes
the radiance of his opponent.
（駿海）
まるで相手の輝きを塗りつぶす黒
The dark carnage of battle!
修羅戦黒(しゅらせんごく)の相！
Hinomaru!
火ノ丸！
Tennoji even anticipates his
opponent's growth and counters to it.
（火ノ丸）天王寺は
相手の成長すら想像し 対応する
なら ワシは 今ここで—
So I've only got one option...
To outperform his expectations!
天王寺の想像を超えてみせる！
（突く音）
何や？
What's this?
殺気が消えた！？
His intensity just tanked.
（礼奈）めった打ち！
He's getting pummeled!
Ushio-kun usually goes for all-out offense,
but now, he's gone defensive.
（咲）いつも前に出る潮君が
守りに徹しとる　打つ手がないんや
He's out of options.
My brother already countered
every single one of his moves.
使える技は 全て兄貴に防がれた
The only other way Ushio-kun can win...
あと 潮君に残された勝ち筋は…
両廻しを取って
崩しからの百千夜叉墜(ひゃくせんやしゃおとし)
is to grab both sides of his belt,
shake him up,
and use the Hundred-Thousand Demon Takedown.
But my brother's belt
is low and out of reach.
でも そのために必要な両廻しが
低くて遠い
That low strike he showed against Kusanagi...
草薙戦で見せた低空の突き
It would be some feat to bypass it
and get close enough to grab his belt.
これをかいくぐって 両廻しを
引くほど近づくんは 至難の業や
Are you gonna be robbed
of your biggest weapon, too?
（典馬）お前まで
消されちまうのか？　持ち味を
のみ込まれちまうのか？　闇に
Will you be swallowed by the darkness?
He pulled back!
（天王寺）引いた！
（典馬）ハッ…
（狩谷(かりや)）おい　なんで引いてんだ？
Hey, now... Why are you pulling back?
お前は
引いたらあかんやろう 火ノ丸
You know you can't afford
to pull back, Hinomaru.
お前は今 認めてもうたんや
By doing that, you've acknowledged
その体での真っ向勝負は
ここが限界やと
that this is as far as you can go
fighting head-on with your physique.
今まで認めてへんかったから
ここまで来れたんやろう？
But you only made it this far
because you never acknowledged that!
Retreating like a coward...
そんな魂のない引きでは
落ちんわ！
is unacceptable!
Was Tennoji's intensity too much for you?
（狩谷）
天王寺の圧力に屈したのかよ？
Weren't you going to show me a path
that I didn't have the courage to take?
俺が選べなかった道を
見せてくれるんじゃなかったのかよ
Don't run away!
逃げてんじゃねえよ…
No.
（久世）いや　逃げてない
He isn't.
His heart's still in it.
心は退(ひ)いてない
Hinomaru has never ceased moving forward.
絶え間なく
前進し続けた火ノ丸が—
He only pulled back to build up momentum
for a more powerful step forward!
より強い１歩を踏み出すための
“溜(た)め”
（火ノ丸）ワシは弱い
I'm weak.
That's why I lost.
だから負けた
ワシひとりの力では届かない
My strength alone wasn't enough.
じゃが 負けたおかげで気づけた
But losing has taught me
that I didn't get where I am by myself!
ワシは ここまで ひとりで
来たわけじゃなかったんじゃ！
（咲）えっ！？
（礼奈）それは…
That's...
（火ノ丸）
毎日 稽古で受ける お前の突きは…
Those strikes you rain down
on me at every practice...
They hurt, Yuma!
（火ノ丸）痛かったぜ 佑真！
A lunge punch!
（佑真）追い突き！
What was that?
（天王寺）なんやと！？
八艘(はっそう)！
A leap!
No...
いや 跳んでへん！
He didn't jump!
Your gung-ho reverse
（火ノ丸）お前の
気迫の籠もった“変化”は—
知ってても
ダマされそうになったもんじゃ 蛍
nearly fools me even
when I'm expecting it, Kei!
He's always been varying his attacks,
interspersing strong moves with weak ones.
（柴木山）攻めの緩急は
今までもあった　強弱という形で
But now...
でも これは…
Pulling back gave him more room to accelerate.
引きが より大きな振り幅となり
助走となり…
His head-on style will shine even brighter!
（柴木山）
真っ向勝負が より強く輝く！
He's using a wider range of attacks now.
（咲）
攻めのパターンが広がっていく…
My brother won't be able to
anticipate them all!
兄貴の想定を超えるほどに！
To him, his sumo equals his way of life.
（駿海）
あいつの相撲は生き方そのもの
“引けばいい”などと
軽々しく口を出せば—
If he thought for one moment
that retreat was acceptable,
his light would have
immediately been extinguished.
たちまち その光は失われただろう
相撲が 生き方が 覚悟が…
Sumo, his way of life, and his resolve...
Each one brings a strength to his eyes.
それぞれの形で その瞳に力を宿す
鬼炎万丈(きえんばんじょう)の相！
The demonic, enduring determination!
Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop!
百千夜叉墜！
I thought that, being
fifth on the roster meant
ワシは大将として みんなに
弱みを見せてはならぬと思っていた
never letting the team view me as weak.
That it meant being strong all the time.
“強くあり続けねばならぬ”と
That it meant always being their leader.
“みんなの先頭に立って
進み続けねばならぬ”と
And if I stopped going forward,
they'd be unable to continue.
“ワシが止まれば みんなの足も
止めてしまう”と そう思っていた
I thought all those things.
でも 違ったんじゃ
But I was wrong.
After I lost, what I saw was
負けて
見上げた先にあったのは—
仲間たちの頼もしい背中じゃった
my reliable teammates walking in front of me.
まだワシは
あんたに全てをぶつけていない！
I haven't hit you with all I've got yet!
My body has the sumo of
my whole team inside it!
ワシの体に刻まれた みんなの相撲
千比路のように自由な相撲！
Chihiro's freestyle sumo!
Falling technique! Backward hook body drop!
（火ノ丸）反り手！　掛け反り！
A falling technique!
反り技！？
左右の投げに 押し　そこに
引きや反りまで加えれば—
Throwing and pushing to both sides,
then adding a pullback and fall...
Even Tennoji won't anticipate that!
天王寺といえど
読み切ることはできない！
Go!
（桐仁）いけー！
（バトムンフ）兄貴！
Boss!
（天王寺）クッ…　おらぁ！
Do you know why I chose Tottori Hakuro?
（天王寺）なんで俺が
鳥取白楼を選んだか分かるか？
さまざまな取り口の
スペシャリストたちと—
Because I face specialists with
a vast array of techniques every day,
毎日 やり合(お)うてきた
どんな相手 どんな状況にも
対応できるように
which means I'm ready for anything
any opponent can throw at me.
仲間たちの強さが 俺を強くした！
My teammates' strength has made me stronger!
You can try to outperform
my expectations all you like.
（天王寺）お前が 俺の想定を
超えようが 何をしてこようが—
I'll still deal with you in an instant!
瞬時に対応してみせる！
（火ノ丸）ウウッ！
（天王寺）俺は強い！
I am strong.
My team has made me the strongest!
仲間が俺を最強にした！
（火ノ丸）ウワッ！
（天王寺）ンンーッ！
Something you noticed
in my bout with Tennoji?
（火ノ丸）
天王寺戦で気づいたこと？
Yes, but I'm not sure
how useful it will be.
はい　役に立つかは分かりませんが
潮君の ほかの試合と
何度も見比べて 間違いないかと
I compared it with your other bouts,
and I'm certain of it.
Right here.
ここです
Don't get overwhelmed!
（火ノ丸）
のみ込まれるな　仕掛け続けろ！
Keep attacking!
Reverse Hundred Demon Takedown!
逆･百鬼薙(ひゃっきなぎ)！
Don't stop! Keep shaking him!
止まるな　もっと揺さぶれ！
勝つまで止まるな！
Don't stop until you win!
百千夜叉墜！
Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop!
You did the Hundred-Thousand
Demon Drop after a push,
押しからの百千夜叉墜
これがかえって 投げの回転力を
弱めていたんだと思います
and I think it actually weakened
the centrifugal force.
This wasn't a full-strength
Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop.
このときの百千夜叉墜は
万全じゃない
この技は
左右に揺さぶれば揺さぶるほど…
The more you shake him from side to side...
威力を増す！
...the more powerful it becomes!
もっとじゃ　天王寺の自由を奪え！
C'mon, more! Make Tennoji lose his footing!
渦巻け 烈火のごとく！
Swirl around him like an inferno!
Reverse Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop!
逆･百千夜叉墜！
（礼奈）
ハァ…　すごいな 堀(ほり)ちゃんは
Hori-chan's really something.
Huh?
I mean, I want to help you guys out, too.
私だって もっと
みんなの力になりたいと思ってるよ
でも 全然ダメ
But I'm no help at all.
No, you are helping.
力になっとるさ
Huh?
This technique...
（火ノ丸）この技は—
Kirihito...
桐仁
The guys at the Shibakiyama Stable...
柴木山部屋のみんな
The two masters...
親方
師匠
ライバルたち
My rivals...
My team...
部員のみんな
そう…
礼奈もいたから 完成したんじゃ
And yes, you too, Reina.
You all helped me complete it.
Tennoji, you are indeed strong.
天王寺　あんたは強い
ワシひとりでは
あんたには勝てねえ
I could never defeat you alone.
But we're not alone anymore,
are we, Captain?
でも ワシらは
もう ひとりじゃなかった
そうじゃろう？　部長
いけ！　潮ーっ！
Go, Ushio!
（火ノ丸）これがワシの全てじゃ！
This is everything I've got!
Demon's
Enduring
Determination
Demon's
Enduring
Determination
Demon's Enduring Determination!
Demon's
Enduring
Determination
Hundred
Thousand
Demon
Drop
Hundred
Thousand
Demon
Drop
Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop!
Hundred
Thousand
Demon
Drop
Go!
いけーっ！
勝てーっ！
Win!
うん？　殺気！？
A menacing aura?
Even at a time like this, you're smiling.
（火ノ丸）こんなときでも
あんたは笑うんじゃな
Kusanagi beat me.
（天王寺）俺は草薙に負けた
俺自身は もう王者やない
I'm no longer a champion.
でもな それでも
俺は王者白楼の大将なんや
But even so, I'm the captain of
the champion Hakuro team.
I have to be the strongest.
最強でなきゃいかんのや
I'll smile even when
I'm on the brink of death!
死の淵(ふち)でも笑え！
俺の強さで あいつらを
いちばん上に連れていくんや！
My strength will take
my team to the very top!
A throw when his body
was about to collapse...
（駿海）
体(たい)が死にきる寸前で 投げを…
What determination!
（柴木山）なんという執念
You really are incredible.
やっぱり あんた すげえよ
（千鶴子）左腕が…
（蛍）限界！？
His left arm...
Is he at his limit?
Even if you've reached your limit,
（礼奈）限界だったとしても
執念こそが—
your determination is your greatest weapon!
あんたの
いちばんの武器でしょう！
どんな窮地でも 折れない 諦めない
No matter how desperate
things look, you don't bend.
You don't give up.
それが あんたの相撲
That's your style of sumo...
Your Hinomaru sumo!
火ノ丸相撲！
（火ノ丸）クオーッ！
I'm glad I idolized you.
（火ノ丸）あんたに憧れて良かった
It wasn't just my team.
仲間たちだけじゃない
あんたも いたから…
Because of you...
I've come this far chasing after
the great mountain known as Tennoji Shido.
天王寺獅童(しどう)という高い山を
目指したから ここまで来れた
I don't know if I've conquered that mountain.
その山を
越えられたかどうかは分からない
今は まだ
あんたのほうが強いのかもしれない
You may still be stronger than me.
でも それでもいい
But...
That's fine.
みんなが紡いでくれた—
Everyone got me here today.
So today...
今日の… 今日の勝利だけは—
I will come out victorious,
死んでも譲らねえ！
even if it kills me!
ハァ…
（駿海）土俵上での
雄たけびや ガッツポーズは不作法
It's considered bad form to yell
or do a victory pose in the sumo ring.
But I hope no one will
blame you for doing so.
だが 誰も責めてくれるな
That shows just how important
それほどまでに重い…
重い１勝だった
this victory was.
Odachi, on the east side, wins 3-2.
（アナウンス）
３−２で 東 大太刀(おおだち)の勝ち！
Dachi High has made it to the final
in their first national tournament!
全国初出場の大太刀が
決勝進出とはな
王者白楼を…
しかも 天王寺を倒して
They beat the reigning champs, Hakuro,
and defeated Tennoji in the process!
Good work.
（首藤(しゅとう)）お疲れさま
Let's go. We've still got the
third-place match to contest.
（榎木(えのき)）行きましょう
３位決定戦もありますしね
アホやな お前ら 俺に気ぃ遣(つこ)うて
You're all idiots.
Don't put on brave faces for my sake.
やめとけや　悔しいときは悔しがれ
When you're disappointed, show it.
（部員たちの泣き声）
そして 心に刻め
Etch it into your heart.
That feeling will become
your strength some day.
この気持ちは
いつか強さにつながる
I let you down, too.
（天王寺）お前も すまんかったな
I couldn't make you the manager
of the best team in Japan.
日本一のチームのマネージャーに
してやれんかったわ
（咲）人のことは ええねん
Forget about me.
Focus on your own feelings for once.
こんなときぐらい
自分の気持ち優先せえよ
My own feelings...
（天王寺）俺の気持ち…
Hinomaru struck a victory pose, huh?
火ノ丸が ガッツポーズか
謝るな　この俺に勝ったんやで
Don't apologize.
You beat me, after all.
そのくらいは喜んでもらわんと
困るわ
I need you to show that much joy at least.
The score is one-all.
お前とは まだ１勝１敗
We'll have our decider in the pro league.
決着は 大相撲の舞台でつけようや
You'd better win and
make it there, Hinomaru.
そのためにも
勝ってプロになれよ　火ノ丸
（四方田(よもだ)）
ハァ…　まだ会場 どよめいてるよ
The crowd's still buzzing from that bout.
（四方田）やりづらいな
まさか 白楼が負けるとは
This is an awkward situation.
Who would've predicted Hakuro would lose?
（兵藤(ひょうどう)）ハハハハッ…　関係ねえな
だったら俺らは—
Who cares?
We'll just have to treat 'em
to a battle with more punch.
白楼と大太刀のインパクトを
超える戦いをするだけよ
（四方田）危ねっ！
（兵藤）さあ 見せてやろうぜ！
Right! Let's show 'em...
what the cream of Eiga
University High has to offer!
栄華(えいが)大附属
ベストメンバーの実力をな！
さすが
土俵の外でも迫力ありますね
He's even intimidating
outside the sumo ring.
That's because he's got no eyebrows.
そりゃ 眉毛がないから
Eyebrows?
（天王寺）眉毛？
（礼奈たち）ハッ…
Oh, I have eyebrows. Look.
あるやん　ほら
ずっと あるやんか　ほら
They've been here the whole time.
（千鶴子）あっ…
（礼奈）あった…
Next Bout    "Idiot and Idiot"
So you do...